https://www.ipmvs.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Privacy & Confidentiality: MVS is committed to protecting the privacy and confidentiality of its clients and website visitors. In general, you can access the Site without providing MVS with any personal information; however, you may provide personal information, such as providing contact information to receive alerts and / or communications from MVS, or you may provide submissions to MVS through the Online Contact Form submissions. Please note that website security is sometimes beyond MVS control. Please do not send confidential information through the Site or through any Online Contact Form submissions available through the Site. MVS cannot guarantee the confidentiality of any communications you send though this Site. Additionally, the firm may collect non-public personal information about you from the information you send through this Site. MVS has implemented 1) remarketing with Google Analytics and 2) Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. MVS and its third-party vendors use first-party cookies to advertise to visitors based on past website visits, demographics and interests. If you wish to opt out of Google’s use of cookies, please visit Google’s Ad Settings. If you wish to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page. We will use your information to respond to you. If you have any questions about your personal information, please contact us.
Please also see our Terms of Use, which describes the restrictions, disclaimers, indemnification and limitation of liability governing the use of the entire web site.
Stay in Touch
Receive the latest news and updates from us and our attorneys.
Sign Up
